aaaagencysearch.com 2005-02-04

# AAAAgencySearch.com > Privacy Policy

|   

| 

Searchers    Agencies  

### Searchers

The American Association of Advertising Agencies and the AAAAgencysearch.com web site respects each individual's right to privacy and we are dedicated to the fundamentals of protecting your privacy on the Internet. 

As a web site user, whether you are an advertiser, search consultant or just a general browser, we understand the importance you place on the privacy of your identity and personal information. The American Association of Advertising Agencies takes every measure possible to assure that all personal information received from registered users is as secure as possible against unauthorized access and use. We extend the following statement to all site visitors in order to ensure the safety and confidentiality of your personal information.

  1. We do not and will not sell your personal information to anyone.
  2. We will only share personal information with others as outlined in this statement, unless we give you additional notice or ask for your permission directly. 
  3. Whenever we collect personal information from you, we use it in ways that are in direct accordance with the purpose and functionality of this web site. We will protect the confidentiality of any personal information you share with us.
  4. We limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business and to deliver this service to you. 
  5. We do not share personal information about search consultants, advertisers, or agencies. 
  6. The AAAA's corporate policies require that those affiliated with the site or working for the AAAA organization who have access to confidential agency information may not use or disclose the information except for business use that is directly in keeping with the purpose and functionality of this web site.
  7. We will not provide participating agencies with specific information about who has viewed their agency profile. This protects the privacy of an advertiser or a searcher. We will, however, provide agencies with data about **how many times** their profile was viewed or downloaded to a portfolio, never **who specifically __**_viewed or downloaded their profile. Agencies will not be able to tell who has accessed their profile_.
  8. All agencies will receive tracking information for their agency only. Agencies will not be privy to web site data for any other agency participating in the database.
  9. We continue to evaluate our own efforts to protect your personal information and we make every effort to keep your personal information accurate and up to date.

If you identify any errors in your company or personal information or need to edit/update that information, you must: 
  * go to <http://www.aaaagencysearch.com/agencylogin/login.asp>, login with your username and password, and proceed to update your profile.
  
 **-or-**  

  * contact Matt Holland at Kintera, Inc. and he will promptly update your records.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us as follows: 

  * Matt Holland, Project Manager, Kintera Inc.  

### Agencies

The AAAA's American Association of Advertising Agencies, and the AAAAgencysearch.com web site respects each individual's right to privacy and we are dedicated to the fundamentals of protecting your privacy on the Internet. Our relationship with your agency is our most valuable asset and is the basis of our name and reputation.

We understand the importance you place on the privacy and the security of the information that personally identifies your agency. We refer to and treat your agency profile as personal information and take every measure possible to assure that agency data is secure against unauthorized access and use. We extentd the following statement to your agency to ensure the safety and confidentiality of both your personal and agency information.

  1. We do not sell your personal or agency information to anyone.
  2. We will only share personal and agency information with others as outlined in this statement, unless we give you additional notice or ask for your permission directly. We do reserve the right to disclose or report information in circumstances directly related to and in accordance with the usage of this search site. 
  3. Whenever we collect personal information from you, we will refer you to this statement, or otherwise explain to you how we intend to use this information. We will protect the confidentiality of any personal or agency information you share with us.

We use personal information in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which we originally requested it. We also use personal information in ways that are in direct accordance with the purpose and functionality of this web site. 

  4. We limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business and to deliver this service to you. This may include advising you on how to use our services, the services of our affiliates, such as the Advertising Jobs Web site or AAAA Benefits, and other opportunities that we feel might interest you. To serve you better, we may combine the information you give us on the web or through other channels.
  5. We will protect the confidentiality of any information you share with us. **** We do not share personal information about search consultants, advertisers, or agencies. Participating agencies, advertisers and search consultants must adhere to our privacy statement.
  6. The AAAA's corporate policies require that those affiliated with the site or working for the AAAA organization who have access to confidential agency information may not use or disclose the information except for business use that is directly in keeping with the purpose and functionality of this web site.
  7. We will not provide agencies with specific information about who has viewed their agency profile. This protects the privacy of an advertiser or a searcher. We will, however, provide agencies with data about **how many times** their profile was viewed or downloaded to a portfolio, never **who specifically __**_viewed or downloaded their profile. Agencies will not be able to tell who has accessed their profile._
 __
  8. All agencies will receive tracking information for their agency only. Agencies will not be privy to web site data for any other agency participating in the database.
  9. We continue to evaluate our own efforts to protect your personal information and we make every effort to help you keep your personal information accurate and up to date.

If you identify any errors in your company or personal information or need to edit/update that information, you must: 
  * go to <http://www.aaaagencysearch.com/agencylogin/login.asp>, login with your username and password, and proceed to update your profile.
  
 **-or-**  

  * contact Matt Holland at Kintera, Inc. and he will promptly update your records.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us as follows: 

  * Matt Holland, Project Manager, Kintera Inc.  

|   

| 

Searchers    Agencies  

### Searchers

The American Association of Advertising Agencies and the AAAAgencysearch.com web site respects each individual's right to privacy and we are dedicated to the fundamentals of protecting your privacy on the Internet. 

As a web site user, whether you are an advertiser, search consultant or just a general browser, we understand the importance you place on the privacy of your identity and personal information. The American Association of Advertising Agencies takes every measure possible to assure that all personal information received from registered users is as secure as possible against unauthorized access and use. We extend the following statement to all site visitors in order to ensure the safety and confidentiality of your personal information.

  1. We do not and will not sell your personal information to anyone.
  2. We will only share personal information with others as outlined in this statement, unless we give you additional notice or ask for your permission directly. 
  3. Whenever we collect personal information from you, we use it in ways that are in direct accordance with the purpose and functionality of this web site. We will protect the confidentiality of any personal information you share with us.
  4. We limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business and to deliver this service to you. 
  5. We do not share personal information about search consultants, advertisers, or agencies. 
  6. The AAAA's corporate policies require that those affiliated with the site or working for the AAAA organization who have access to confidential agency information may not use or disclose the information except for business use that is directly in keeping with the purpose and functionality of this web site.
  7. We will not provide participating agencies with specific information about who has viewed their agency profile. This protects the privacy of an advertiser or a searcher. We will, however, provide agencies with data about **how many times** their profile was viewed or downloaded to a portfolio, never **who specifically __**_viewed or downloaded their profile. Agencies will not be able to tell who has accessed their profile_.
  8. All agencies will receive tracking information for their agency only. Agencies will not be privy to web site data for any other agency participating in the database.
  9. We continue to evaluate our own efforts to protect your personal information and we make every effort to keep your personal information accurate and up to date.

If you identify any errors in your company or personal information or need to edit/update that information, you must: 
  * go to <http://www.aaaagencysearch.com/agencylogin/login.asp>, login with your username and password, and proceed to update your profile.
  
 **-or-**  

  * contact Matt Holland at Kintera, Inc. and he will promptly update your records.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us as follows: 

  * Matt Holland, Project Manager, Kintera Inc.  

### Agencies

The AAAA's American Association of Advertising Agencies, and the AAAAgencysearch.com web site respects each individual's right to privacy and we are dedicated to the fundamentals of protecting your privacy on the Internet. Our relationship with your agency is our most valuable asset and is the basis of our name and reputation.

We understand the importance you place on the privacy and the security of the information that personally identifies your agency. We refer to and treat your agency profile as personal information and take every measure possible to assure that agency data is secure against unauthorized access and use. We extentd the following statement to your agency to ensure the safety and confidentiality of both your personal and agency information.

  1. We do not sell your personal or agency information to anyone.
  2. We will only share personal and agency information with others as outlined in this statement, unless we give you additional notice or ask for your permission directly. We do reserve the right to disclose or report information in circumstances directly related to and in accordance with the usage of this search site. 
  3. Whenever we collect personal information from you, we will refer you to this statement, or otherwise explain to you how we intend to use this information. We will protect the confidentiality of any personal or agency information you share with us.

We use personal information in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which we originally requested it. We also use personal information in ways that are in direct accordance with the purpose and functionality of this web site. 

  4. We limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business and to deliver this service to you. This may include advising you on how to use our services, the services of our affiliates, such as the Advertising Jobs Web site or AAAA Benefits, and other opportunities that we feel might interest you. To serve you better, we may combine the information you give us on the web or through other channels.
  5. We will protect the confidentiality of any information you share with us. **** We do not share personal information about search consultants, advertisers, or agencies. Participating agencies, advertisers and search consultants must adhere to our privacy statement.
  6. The AAAA's corporate policies require that those affiliated with the site or working for the AAAA organization who have access to confidential agency information may not use or disclose the information except for business use that is directly in keeping with the purpose and functionality of this web site.
  7. We will not provide agencies with specific information about who has viewed their agency profile. This protects the privacy of an advertiser or a searcher. We will, however, provide agencies with data about **how many times** their profile was viewed or downloaded to a portfolio, never **who specifically __**_viewed or downloaded their profile. Agencies will not be able to tell who has accessed their profile._
 __
  8. All agencies will receive tracking information for their agency only. Agencies will not be privy to web site data for any other agency participating in the database.
  9. We continue to evaluate our own efforts to protect your personal information and we make every effort to help you keep your personal information accurate and up to date.

If you identify any errors in your company or personal information or need to edit/update that information, you must: 
  * go to <http://www.aaaagencysearch.com/agencylogin/login.asp>, login with your username and password, and proceed to update your profile.
  
 **-or-**  

  * contact Matt Holland at Kintera, Inc. and he will promptly update your records.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us as follows: 

  * Matt Holland, Project Manager, Kintera Inc.
